♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
[Samir, in English] The man who broke
into the ambassador's office.
[in English] He might be here too.
[gunshots]
[screaming and panicking]
Son of a thread.
[Mercado on phone]
Lily Santiago is the head
of the IT of the embassy.
[in English] Where is she?
[grunts]
PREVIOUSLY
[sobbing]
[Samir, in English] Where is the girl?
[wails]
[armed man] Sir, they're here, sir!
[on phone] We're about to catch them, sir!
[grunts and groans]
[grunting]
[gunshots]
[Samir, in English]
Before I do something to you,
I want to see your face.
[Charmi] Friend, maybe you should
focus on Ibyang first.
[Olga] Maybe you're right.
The child hasn't done anything wrong
for me to treat her that way.
Even my own child.
[in English] This has to stop!
You're a monster!
This is the first time
I've had such a beautiful doll.
[Olga] You're a meddler!
Did I tell you to take this?!
[Red, in English] I'm sure
you know that seal, right?
[in English] He is the mastermind!
[in English] What's going on here?
[in English] Are you involved
in human trafficking?
[in English] Audrey, let me explain.
[in English] I trusted you!
[Audrey] I chose you over Atoy!
But you were deceiving me!
Brother! Psst, hey!
Brother! [sobs]
[in English] I'm sorry.
I didn't tell you everything.
I stepped down from the business
and let Red take over.
But you're still part of it!
[in English] That doesn't make you
any less guilty, Dad!
And you even used Bahay Kayakap
as a front to do evil!
Don't you feel any shame
for what you've been doing?
- Audrey, I am not going to justify--
- You
rescue women only to harm them further?
Do you really have no conscience?!
[dark sinister music playing]
[in English] Like I said,
I'm not going to justify anything,
and I know you don't want
to be a part of this.
But this…
- This has become our family's business.
- [scoffs]
Even if it hurts me…
[in English] But you can leave this house,
leave the country.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Go wherever you want.
[in English] Take Janine with you
and start anew.
Don't put this family in danger.
[in English] Please, my child. Please?
[in English] So, you want me to look away?
[in English] To turn a blind eye?
[in English] All I'm asking you
is to consider your family.
We're not perfect,
but I hope you choose us.
[in English] Just the way your mother
chose our family over everything.
Your mother knew all of this.
[in English] She never agreed.
But family weighed more for her.
[Audrey, in English] Dad?
Dad, what's happening?
- [in English] Dad, sit, sit, sit.
- [groans]
[pensive music playing]
[Audrey gasps]
[Audrey] You need to be taken
to the hospital.
Gavin!
Gavin, take Dad to the hospital!
[Dmitri] Audrey.
[in English] Please, promise me.
You won't do anything
with what you've learned.
[in English] Please, child.
I'm just a little stressed,
that's why my wound opened.
[in English] Please? Please, my child.
Gavin!
- [Audrey] Gavin!
- Auntie?
- Auntie!
- Take Dad to the hospital!
- His wound is bleeding.
- Grandpa.
- I'll follow.
- Okay, Auntie.
Come on, Grandpa.
[sinister music playing]
If it's Audrey,
Dad is very easy to persuade.
[in English] That's a fact.
‪[scoffs]
[mysterious music playing]
[in English] Gavin just messaged again.
We really need to go to the hospital.
[in English] We have to see your dad,
especially you.
[suspicious music playing]
No.
We'll stay here.
[in English] Why?
[music fades]
[suave theme music playing]
[music swells]
[electronic blipping]
[grunts]
[pants and sobs]
[Lily, in English] I don't know
where it is!
[in English] And I don't know who…
[in English] I don't know
who he is, I told you.
[in English] I've never--
I've never met him in my entire life!
[in English] You are lying!
[in English] I am not lying. [sobs]
[in English] Then why did he try
to protect you? Hmm?
[Samir, in English] Why did he try
to save you?
‪[Lily sobs]
[in English] It's because you two
are working together!
[tense music playing]
Huh?
[Lily pants]
[in English] We are not working together.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Well, well, well.
[in English] Look who decided
to join the party.
[in English] Good morning.
[in English] You are ready
to talk now, yes?
[in English] Let's make this simple.
[in English] Yes?
[in English] I will ask you a question.
[in English] If you answer, you can go.
[suspicious music playing]
[Samir, in English] But
if you don't…
you will not go.
[in English] Yes?
[in English] Where is the laptop?
Mmm.
[in English] Okay.
You don't want to talk to me.
[in English] I see.
- [grunts]
- [in English] No, no, no, no, no!
- [Lily, in English] No!
[Lily sobs]
[Atoy coughs]
[tense music playing]
[in English] So,
if you don't want to talk…
maybe we can play a little game.
- [in English] Yes?
- [in English] Yes!
[in English] You like games?
[groans]
[in English] Yes.
- [Samir, in English] Perfect.
- [groans]
[sobs]
[ominous music playing]
[dagger clatters]
[in English] Cut him.
[in English] Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
[Lily] Please! Don't, don't, don't, don't.
Brother, don't!
[grunts]
[in English] If you do not
want to make this simple,
I will make it very, very hard for you.
[pensive music playing]
[grunts]
[in English] You tell me now.
[in English] Who are you working for?
[in English] And where is my briefcase?
[heavy music playing]
[in English] Okay.
[in English] I will, I will…
I will tell you.
[in English] The briefcase is…
[in English] Briefcase is…
- in my…
- [in English] In your?
[in English] In my nose.
[tense music playing]
[in English] No!
Stop, please!
[Lily sobs] No.
[sobbing] No, please!
[Samir, in English]
Where is my briefcase?!
[Samir, in English] Three, two, one!
- [grunts]
- [Lily shrieks]
[in English] No!
[Lily, in English] Please, stop it!
[in English] Who are you working for?!
[panting]
[in English] Three, two, one!
- [groans]
- [Lily wails, in English] No!
[in English] Tell me
where my briefcase is.
[in English] Do you want to talk?
[in English] Yes. It is
in your, in your… in your pocket!
- [in English] In your left pocket.
- [growls]
[grunts]
[groaning and growling]
- [grunts]
- [Lily wailing]
[groans and wails, in English] No!
- [Samir groans]
- [grunts]
[heavy pained breathing]
- [Lily, in English] No, no. Please, no!
- [grunts]
- [groans]
- [Lily wailing]
[ominous music playing]
[in English] Are you ready to tell me now
where my laptop is?
[in English] Nope? Okay.
[Lily, in English] No! No!
- [Samir, in English] Yes.
- [in English] Are you… Are you tired?
[in English] You, you whip
so, so, so weak!
[cackles]
[speaking in Russian]
I'll beat the living hell…
[indistinct]
[speaking in Russian] …you bastard!
[speaking in Visayan]
Please, stop it already!
[wailing, indistinct]
[coughs]
[grunts]
[sobbing]
[music fades]
Hey, Ibyang!
[Charmi] Ibyang!
[melancholic music playing]
What are you doing there?
Why is the pretty child crying?
Hey.
Mama scolded me.
[sobs] Then she said I'm not her child.
What happened?
Why did Mama Olga scold you?
Because I broke the doll
that I thought was a gift for me.
Hmm, the doll.
You know, Ibyang?
That's just how Mama Olga is.
She's sometimes strict.
You know, sometimes when we fight,
we have misunderstandings.
She even tells me
we're not friends anymore.
But that's not true,
because we're friends no matter what.
[in English] Through thick and thin,
through sickness and in health.
[in English] So help me, God.
‪[quirky sting]
Well…
That's just how your Mama Olga is.
She's sometimes strict.
But even if she's stern sometimes,
she's kind most of the time.
She's crazy, but very kind.
That's why I'm sure she didn't mean
to say you're not her child.
You are her child. You are her daughter.
Come on, oh! Look, you even look alike!
[Charmi chuckles, in English] Olga Junior!
[melodramatic music playing]
Mmm.
Just be patient with Mama Olga,
okay, child.
Go upstairs now.
She might get angry if she can't find you.
Go on. Go now.
Stop crying. Stop crying, stop crying.
Smile now, okay?
Smile.
[softly, in English] Pajamas.
[in English] Mommy.
Are we leaving?
[in English] Yes, child.
Where are we going?
To the States.
To America?
Yay!
I'll finally see snow!
Child, my child, my child. Wait, wait.
Listen first.
I'm sorry if this trip is sudden.
But we need to visit
your Daddy Atoy first.
- [in English] Okay?
- Okay.
Go get dressed now.
[tense music playing]
[melancholic music playing]
[in English] Sorry, Mama.
[sobs] Because of me,
the doll was broken.
[sobs] It won't happen again. Promise.
[in English] I love you, Mama.
[in English] Let's go, child.
Ma'am, are you leaving?
Yes. Please open the gate.
Ah. Okay, ma'am.
I'm so excited, Mommy!
It's my dream to go to America!
[tense music playing]
- Get in, child.
- [Janine, in English] Okay.
[in English] Let me help you
with your seatbelt, dear.
[Janine, in English] Mommy, Mommy.
Are you in a hurry?
No one leaves.
[Red] Try to start that.
Try it.
[line ringing]
What happened to you, Padua?
[automated voice, in English]
Please try your call later.
[keyboard clicks]
My husband is now in the hospital.
[in English] I know as a mayor, my husband
has several death threats.
Whoever entered and caused trouble
in my home,
we will make sure you are punished.
[line ringing]
[in English] I need you
to report to me in person.
- [in English] Padua is compromised.
- [rousing music playing]
- Stop it!
- Aunt Martina!
[in English] Martina, stop!
- [in English] Stop!
- [in English] Mommy!
You're hurting her!
Stop it! Let her go!
- You're too noisy.
- Red!
- [in English] Mommy, Mommy!
- Please! Put down your gun!
The child is scared!
Martina is hurting her! Stop it! Stop!
[gasps, in English] Mommy.
Sir Red, I'm sorry.
I heard Ma'am Janine
and Ma'am Audrey shouting.
- I thought--
- What did you think, huh?
No one leaves this house.
Lock the gate.
Don't tell anyone.
Don't say you saw anything.
If you want to go home to your family.
Clear?
Yes.
- Go now.
- Okay.
Where are you going?
To the hospital.
We're going to see Dad at the hospital.
In case you didn't know,
his wound got worse.
Hospital, but you're bringing
your luggage?
What's that, a vacation?
You even brought this evidence
that could ruin your family.
[in English] No… No, Red.
I promised Dad I wouldn't speak out.
[in English] Please, just let us go.
[grunts and groans]
[in English] Mommy?
[screams]
- [in English] Mommy! Mommy!
- [Red] Take them to my old room!
[in English] Mommy!
Make sure you dispose of Audrey's car.
Let me go! Mommy!
[bawling]
[in English] Mommy! Mommy!
[wails]
Mommy! Please, wake up!
Mommy! Why did you bring me
and my mommy here?!
You're all cruel!
[squeals]
Be quiet.
And stop with your "Mommy, Mommy"!
[whimpering]
This is just their temporary cell.
They can't stay here long.
Dad might come back.
[in English] So,
what's your plan with them?
There are many things we can do with them.
Especially with the child.
We can use her to make money.
You, get a gag and ropes for these two.
And no one should know they're here. Okay?
[tense music playing]
[sobs]
[music fades]
[Charmi clears throat]
Friend?
Friend!
Ibyang?
Ibyang, wake up.
Wake up, child. Wake up.
[Charmi] Oh? Have you reconciled
with Mama Olga?
Where's your mama?
Friend! Olga!
Frie…
Mama slept here.
I slept beside her.
Maybe she's still angry with me.
[melancholic music playing]
[clears throat]
Just let your Mama Olga be.
She just went out. She'll come back.
Who is Sammy?
Because Mama mentioned her name
last night while crying.
Ah. [sighs]
Ibyang, because it's not really…
It's not really for me to tell.
But Mama might not tell me herself.
I just want to understand her.
Does Mama have another child?
- Uh…
- Is it Sammy?
Where is she?
Um…
[sighs]
Child, Sammy is Mama Olga's child
who died.
So, she's your sibling.
Why didn't Mama tell me
that I had a sibling?
Let's just try to understand Mama Olga.
Because it's painful for her.
That's why she's sad.
Can you do that?
[music fades]
[ominous music playing]
[gasping]
[tense sinister music playing]
‪[groans]
[muttering and sobbing]
[Audrey] My child.
‪My child.
‪[whimpers]
‪[Audrey] No!
[Mongki, in English]
Good morning, Ms. Audrey.
[wailing and muttering]
- [Mongki] Good night again.
- [wailing and muttering]
[Mongki] Sleep soundly there.
Just like your baby girl.
[music fades]
[wailing and muttering]
[tense music playing]
[electronic blipping]
[intense music playing]
Can you take the child from me?
[Olga on the phone] I quit.
I'm already annoyed with her.
- [Olga] She's too meddlesome.
- [wailing]
- [shrieks]
UP NEXT
[in English] Mama!
[grunts] Help us!
- [Emerson coughs]
- [screaming and panicking]
Oh, no!
Emerson's Tailoring Shop is burning!
- [grunts]
- Emerson!
Ouch!
[screaming and panicking]
[firetruck siren wailing]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ Fix this ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias